Ugh, these shoes stink horribly.
I could
spray some kind of shoe deodorant in there, but afterwards
it would still smell like
sweaty feet, just with a lemon scent.  And
the real problem is that it stays
in the shoe, and that's the moisture.
21% and warmth, an ideal breeding ground.  Combined
with heat, bacteria create a stench,
and
dust dryers help prevent
this stench from developing in the first place.
Price is not the point.  The €16 link
is in the box or scan the QR CD for €16.98,
and because it has a total of four holders,
we can also put a few, i.e., four,
shoes on it.  I'm curious to see
if we'll receive a warm
welcome from Uncle Kramer.  It's
always about tips and tricks, or
anything that might
help you.  Today it's about smelly
shoes.  Of course, we need
230 volts, and some of you know that after
a hard day at work you take off your
shoes and everyone else leaves
the room.  And it gets especially bad
when moisture gets trapped inside due to rain,
sweat, sports, or anything else,
and, most importantly, stays trapped inside.  And
as already mentioned,
you can forget about spray-through deodorant.  I
might be able to mask the smell, but
in my opinion, it sometimes makes it even
worse.  It then really smells sweaty and
lemony, and in this environment
bacteria spread, and
these bacteria are what cause
it to smell quite normal.  And to prevent that from
happening, we use this part
here.  Incidentally, I came up with the idea of
introducing one because
normally a mopping robot stinks,
and my new mopping robot has a
mop heater.  This means that they are dried immediately after
washing, and
consequently no
odor develops, because where there is no moisture
, bacteria cannot
survive.  So, we have a total of
four such air vents here, which we can
adjust and then fix in place.  Then
we can extend the whole thing here; depending on
what kind of shoes
we have or what shoe sizes we have,
we put it up here.  And to be
honest, I thought the price was quite
reasonable.  I've included several in the info box in
case the price
ever increases here, because it's usually
an introductory offer to attract
the first reviews and purchases
.  Therefore, don't just
order blindly.  Shoes are on, he
always does it at 48°.  We can
adjust everything here.
You can hear the volume; we have low, we have
high, and we can also
set a time.  I think
the shoes would be dry after an hour
, but that way the water doesn't run
continuously.  So, set the time
and we'll go to high.  And after
the set time has elapsed, it
simply switches off.  It doesn't stink.  The
inner shoes also receive a
UV light treatment.  Yes, 48° is
n't quite right, I would say.  But you do
n't want to burn the place down either.
Ah, that will be nice and warm.  Sure, you
can also turn up the heating.  The
heating system loses power and
no longer heats the room because the
air circulation is no longer adequate
.  You can also
stuff it with newspaper, of course.  Yes, it's possible.
But it's never as dry as when you
blow-dry it.  I
can really imagine using it in winter, when it
's cold outside, to
preheat my shoes for an hour beforehand.
How did people manage to survive in the past
?  Okay, an hour later
we'll take a look at the shoes.  And
quite honestly, I only
bought it because the price was right, and it
was even cheaper than at Action.  They were available there for
a while, too.
[snorting] So, the inside of the shoe, yes,
it's so dry that it's
barely
showing anything anymore.  So, if anything, 5%.  The
question is, how does it feel?  There's
nothing better than slipping into warm shoes
.  The MV is significantly
reduced.  It must be said quite clearly that
if you do that from the beginning, it wo
n't even arise in the first place.  But for just a
few bucks, I think it's a cool
idea, and it certainly wo
n't win any design awards, but
it doesn't have to dry like shoes anymore.
So much for the topic of keeping your Krammer
clean, tidy and decent.  Hi, just a
quick heads-up: I'm not sponsored,
so I'd appreciate it if you
used the purchase link in the description.
This does not increase the price of the products.  I
only receive a small commission.
M.